### Davi Nomoeh Dani

 ♥ Central Java, ID □(62) 823-2544-1718 @davinomoehdanino@gmail.com

 ⊕ dapino.my.id

I'm a **Software Engineer** who is passionate about learning new things. 3 years of experience in developing, working and contributing to several projects, especially in **backend development**. I am currently employed at a company. Looking for a new job as my next career journey to sharpen up my technology knowledge & experiences in the Technology Industry.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

#### **PT Jawara Solusi Nusantara**

Semarang, ID

#### **Backend Engineer**

September 2022 - Present

- **Project:** Pesan.io (Hotel Booking Platform)
- Spearheaded NodeJS app maintenance and deployment on AWS servers, enhancing performance and reliability
- Optimized compiler configurations, slashing deployment time by 80%
- Developed a Business Intelligence app facilitating seamless integration of external data resources, empowering client system integrations
- Engineered a module for client-loyalty provider integration, enabling customer reward offerings
- Crafted a WhatsApp Chatbot, simplifying hotel room bookings via chat
- Skills: Nest.js (Typescript), AWS, Docker, MongoDB, DevOps, Bash, Process Improvement,
   Container, Jest, CI/CD

## PT TRAVELOKA INDONESIA

Tangerang, ID

# **Backend Engineer Intern (Cloud)**

February 2022 - July 2022

- Orchestrated migration of application infrastructure to AWS serverless platform, utilizing AWS ECS Fargate & AWS Codepipeline
- Proficiently provisioned AWS Infrastructure via Terraform
- Effectively communicated and educated stakeholders on new container stack deployment
- Collaborated across multiple teams, fostering enhanced communication and teamwork
- Minimize the same actions with creating a bot using Node.Js with research
- Skills: Working proficiency in English, Java Spring Boot, AWS, DevOps, Bash, Terraform, Datadog, Process Improvement, Container, CI/CD

# SRW&CO.

Jakarta, ID

Fullstack Engineer Intern
October 2021 - February 2022

- Project: Profesi.io (The Future of Al-driven People Management)
- Led the development of Profesi.io, integrating Al-driven people management tools using Adonis.js and PostgreSQL
- Implemented heavy computing for personalized content, enhancing user recommendations
- Revamped Admin Dashboard UI per Figma specifications with Nuxt.js
- Integrated AgGrid and Quill Editor, customizing modules for developmental needs
- Skills: Adonis.js, Nuxt.js, Typescript, Redis, PostgreSQL, Vue.js

#### **PERSONAL PROJECTS**

# **Supirbarang.com - Simplify delivery process**

- Build an Android App (Flutter), Backend REST API (Nest.js, AWS, MongoDB), and Admin Panel (Next.is)
- Improved performance by migrating stacks from Full Stack Laravel to NestJs, reducing data load time by 60%
- Reduce 30K data load time by up to 60%
- Acquired 1 additional client this year
- View more on: <a href="https://supirbarang.com">https://supirbarang.com</a> and <a href="https://supirbarang.com">Supir Barang on Play Store</a>

# **Vooka - Interactive Music Bot for Discord**

- Stack: Built with Node.js (Typescript) & Discord.js; Store client data to the Database (PostgreSQL)
- **Challenges**: Handle search based on queries with autocomplete and return related playlist; Handles even-loop while the bot is used by multiple users.
- View more on: <a href="https://vookav2.github.io">https://vookav2.github.io</a>

#### **EDUCATION**

Dian Nuswantoro University (Udinus)

Semarang, ID

**Bachelor of Informatics Engineering, Major in Computer Science**August 2019 - February 2023

• GPA: **3.79**/4.0 (7th semester)

**Computer & Network Engineering, Science** 

SMK Tunas Harapan Pati

Pati, ID

January 2016 - October 2019

• Competitions: Android-app innovation (Team); IT Software Application (2nd Winner)

## **AWARD & CERTIFICATION**

• Associate Data Scientist - LSP Udinus July 2022

• Backend Laravel Development - Hacktiv8 March 2022

• Operating Systems and You: Becoming a Power User - May 2020

Coursera

Android Developer (Java) - Dicoding Academy
 December 2019

• 2nd Winner of IT Software Application - LKS Jawa Tengah October 2018

XXVII

Web Developer (PHP Codeigniter) - Trainit October 2017

# **OTHER**

Languages: Basic English, Fluent Bahasa Indonesia (native)

**Technical Skills:** Python, Jupyter Notebook, Golang, Heroku, Google Cloud Platform (GCP) [other skills

from the job description]

Familiars: Blockchain, WEB 3 Technology